hello everyone on behalf of icsa london
i'm extremely pleased to accept this
award and thank you to asia's most
trusted brand and leaders award
this award is a testament to all that we
believe in as an organization
and our brand ethos of nimhyavade which
is the cornerstone and lighthouse of our
focus on customer centricity and value
creation for all our stakeholders
last year was also significant for us as
it marked the integration with party axa
and with this merger icsl lombard has
grown stronger and it has only fueled
our ambitions further
we remain committed to partnering our
customers not just as their risk and
insurance partner but also their overall
well-being partner
thank you once again for this award